Preliminary Guide to the Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records, 1952-2000 MS2083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mutual Radio Theater/Zero Hour, Circa 1973-1980; Series 1; 31.5 Linear Feet
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 153)
    Item Title: Week 2, #9 "The House Call" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 154)
    Item Title: Week 2, #10 "The Violation" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 155)
    Item Title: Week 2, #10 "The Violation" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/06/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 156)
    Item Title: #11 "At Arm's Length" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 157)
    Item Title: Week 3, #12 "Some People Die Only Once" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 158)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 159)
    Item Title: Week 3, #13 "The Reward" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 160)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 161)
    Item Title: Week 3, #14 "Villainous Verdict" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 162)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 163)
    Item Title: Week 3, #15 "The Strange Odyssey of Sandy Mitchell" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 164)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 165)
    Item Title: Week 4, #16 "White Flame Burning Bright" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 166)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 167)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 168)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 169)
    Item Title: Week 4, #17 "Mind of the Beholder" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 170)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 171)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 172)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 173)
    Item Title: Week 4, #18 "Why is Ted Marcosey Driving Aunt Sally Insane" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 174)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 175)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Reel 176)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 177)
    Item Title: Week 4, #19 "There's a Man in 211" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 178)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 179)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 180)
    Item Title: Week 4, #20 "Death is the Puppeteer" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 181)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 182)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 183)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 184)
    Item Title: Week 5, #21 "Dr. Rivington Presumably" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 185)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 186)
    Item Title: Week 5, #21 "Dr. Rivington Presumably" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/22/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 187)
    Item Title: Week 5, #22 "Wanted: A Willing Companion" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/23/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 188)
    Item Title: Week 5, #22 "Wanted: A Willing Companion" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 189)
    Item Title: Week 5, #23 "Pigs Could Put You In The Pen" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 190)
    Item Title: Week 5, #23 "Pigs Could Put You In The Pen" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/23/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 191)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 192)
    Item Title: Week 5, #24 "Sky Lab Are You There" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 193)
    Item Title: Week 5, #24 "Sky Lab Are You There" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/23/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 10, Reel 194)
    Item Title: Week 5, #24 "Sky Lab Are You There" Copy Details: Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/31/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 195)
    Item Title: Week 5, #25 "A Favor You Can't Refuse" Copy Details: Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/23/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/31/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 196)
    Item Title: Week 5, #25 "A Favor You Can't Refuse" Copy Details: Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/31/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 197)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 198)
    Item Title: #26, "Death at Half a Length" Copy Details: Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 199)
    Item Title: #26, "Death at Half a Length" Copy Details: Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 200)
    Item Title: Week 6, #27 "Floating Down the River" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 201)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 202)
    Item Title: Week 6, #28 "Once a Theif" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 203)
    Item Title: Week 6, #28 "Once a Theif" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 204)
    Item Title: Week 6, #29 "Other Sins Only Speak, Murder Shrieks Out" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 205)
    Item Title: Week 6, #29 "Other Sins Only Speak, Murder Shrieks Out" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 206)
    Item Title: Week 6, #30 "The Rehabilitation of Citizen Fimple" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 207)
    Item Title: Week 6, #30 "The Rehabilitation of Citizen Fimple" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 208)
    Item Title: Week 7, #31 "Bonnie and Clyde are as Alive and Living as Mary and Bill" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 209)
    Item Title: Week 7, #31 "Bonnie and Clyde are as Alive and Living as Mary and Bill" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 210)
    Item Title: Week 7, #32 "Sisters of Satan" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 11, Reel 211)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 212)
    Item Title: Week 7, #32 "Sisters of Satan" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 213)
    Item Title: Week 7, #33 "Double Date to Destiny" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 214)
    Item Title: Week 7, #33 "Double Date to Destiny" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 215)
    Item Title: Week 7, #34 "The Mannikin Sham" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 216)
    Item Title: Week 7, #34 "The Mannikin Sham" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 217)
    Item Title: Week 8, #35 "Clay Pigeon" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 218)
    Item Title: Week 8, #36 "The Past Is Always Present" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 219)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 220)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 221)
    Item Title: Week 8, #36 "The Past Is Always Present" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 222)
    Item Title: Week 8, #37 "The Woman In Black" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 223)
    Item Title: Week 8, #37 "The Woman In Black" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 224)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 225)
    Item Title: Week 8, #38 "Come Light My Fire" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 226)
    Item Title: Week 8, #38 "Come Light My Fire" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 227)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 228)
    Item Title: Week 8, #39 "Riders Wanted: Share Expenses" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 12, Reel 229)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 230)
    Item Title: Week 8, #39 "Riders Wanted: Share Expenses" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 231)
    Item Title: Week 8, #40 "Death on Canvas" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 232)
    Item Title: Week 8, #40 "Death on Canvas" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 233)
    Item Title: Week 9, #41 "The House That Clement Built" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 234)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 235)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 236)
    Item Title: Week 9, #41 "The House That Clement Built" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 237)
    Item Title: Week 9, #42 "The Joint Account" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 238)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 239)
    Item Title: Week 9, #42 "The Joint Account" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 240)
    Item Title: Week 9, #43" The Tiger Cages" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 241)
    Item Title: Week 9, #43" The Tiger Cages" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 242)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 243)
    Item Title: Week 9, #44 "Violence Takes a Curtain Call" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 244)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 245)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 246)
    Item Title: Week 9, #44 "Violence Takes a Curtain Call" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Reel 247)
    Item Title: Week 9, #45 "The Children Are Dying" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 248)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 249)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 250)
    Item Title: Week 9, #45 "The Children Are Dying" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 251)
    Item Title: Week 10, #46 "Bend, Spindle and Mutilate" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 252)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 253)
    Item Title: Week 10, #46 "Bend, Spindle and Mutilate" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 254)
    Item Title: Week 10, #47 "Murder is a Work of Art" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 06/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 255)
    Item Title: Week 10, #48 "Edwards Tug and Salvage" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/17/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 256)
    Item Title: #1 "The Wife of the Red-Haired Man", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/18/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 257)
    Item Title: #1 "The Wife of the Red-Haired Man", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/19/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 258)
    Item Title: #1 "The Wife of the Red-Haired Man", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/20/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 259)
    Item Title: #1 "The Wife of the Red-Haired Man", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/21/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 260)
    Item Title: #1 "The Wife of the Red-Haired Man", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/24/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 261)
    Item Title: #2 "The Desperate Witness", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/25/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 262)
    Item Title: #2 "The Desperate Witness", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/26/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 263)
    Item Title: #2 "The Desperate Witness", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/27/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 264)
    Item Title: #2 "The Desperate Witness", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/28/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 265)
    Item Title: #2 "The Desperate Witness", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/31/1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 266)
    Item Title: #3 "If the Two of them are Dead", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Reel 267)
    Item Title: #3 "If the Two of them are Dead", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 268)
    Item Title: #3 "If the Two of them are Dead", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 269)
    Item Title: #3 "If the Two of them are Dead", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 270)
    Item Title: #3 "If the Two of them are Dead", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 271)
    Item Title: #4 "Fourth of Forever", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 272)
    Item Title: #4 "Fourth of Forever", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 273)
    Item Title: #4 "Fourth of Forever", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 274)
    Item Title: #4 "Fourth of Forever", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 275)
    Item Title: #4 "Fourth of Forever", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 276)
    Item Title: #5 "But I Wouldn't Want to Die There", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 277)
    Item Title: #5 "But I Wouldn't Want to Die There", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 278)
    Item Title: #5 "But I Wouldn't Want to Die There", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 279)
    Item Title: #5 "But I Wouldn't Want to Die There", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 280)
    Item Title: #5 "But I Wouldn't Want to Die There", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 281)
    Item Title: #6 "Dead Man's Tale", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 282)
    Item Title: #6 "Dead Man's Tale", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 283)
    Item Title: #6 "Dead Man's Tale", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 284)
    Item Title: #6 "Dead Man's Tale", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 285)
    Item Title: #6 "Dead Man's Tale", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 286)
    Item Title: #7 "The Heir Hunters", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 15, Reel 287)
    Item Title: #7 "The Heir Hunters", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 288)
    Item Title: #7 "The Heir Hunters", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/31/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 289)
    Item Title: #7 "The Heir Hunters", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 290)
    Item Title: #7 "The Heir Hunters", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 291)
    Item Title: #9 "Someon's Death", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 292)
    Item Title: #9 "Someon's Death", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 293)
    Item Title: #9 "Someon's Death", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 294)
    Item Title: #9 "Someon's Death", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 295)
    Item Title: #9 "Someon's Death", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 296)
    Item Title: #10 "Face of the Foe", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 297)